안녕하세요, 척이예요
몇 가지 아셔야 할게 있어요.
Hi, i am chuck.
Here are a few things that you might need to know.
질!
Jill!
널 차 버리고 상처주고
There's no scenario in which
you should be going to dinner
네 제일 친한 친구랑 자기까지한
여자애하고 저녁을 왜 먹어
with the girl that dumped you,
broke your heart and slept with your best friend.
네 가짜 여자친구는 어떻게 해?
질투하지 않을까?
What about your cover girlfriend?
Won't she be jealous?
아니야 우린 그냥 위장커플이라
Our relationship's a cover.
질투하고 그런거 없어
You know, there's nothing
to be jealous about.
척, 내 상사이신
기 르플뢰르씨야
Chuck this is my boss,
Guy LeFleur.
안녕하세요 반갑습니다
Hi. Nice to meet you.
MI-6에 따르면
생화학 무기를 만들어서
MI-6 has reports that
he may have developed
더 높은 값을 쳐주는 사람에게
팔 예정인것 같다는군
a bioweapon which he plans
to sell to the highest bidder.
워커 요원이 죽인 암살범은
풀크럼 요원으로 밝혀졌네
The assassin Agent Walker shot
was a member of FULCRUM.
풀크럼이 질에게
접촉해올 가능성이 있어
If Jill knows something,
they may make a play for her.
센서가 20초간
작동하지 않을거야
The sensor will be blind
for 20 seconds.
국제적인 첩보 세상에 오신걸 환영합니다
Welcome to the world
of international espionage.
소풍오기 딱 좋은 곳이지
Very handy for picnics.
근데 난 아직도 네가
어떻게 스파이가 된건지 모르겠어
I have to say, I still can't wrap my head
around the idea of you as a spy.
어떻게 된건지
나한테 말 안해줬잖아
You never told me
how that happened.
음 그게..
Uh... well...
직업은 네가 선택하는게 아니잖아
You don't choose your
profession, Jill.
직업이 널 선택하는거지
The right job chooses you.
그래도 눈치조차 못 챘을거야
Still-- never
would've guessed it.
이 로맨틱한 경치에 집중해봐
Well, how about you soak
up this romantic view.
그래 퍽이나 로맨틱하다
Yeah, real romantic.
뭐? 여기 바이모어 옥상이라고
What? This is
the Buy More roof.
냄새나? 지금 이 냄새 느껴져?
You smell that? You smell what
you're smelling right now?
옥상 공기는 아무나 못 맡는다고
That is rarefied air, that very
few people ever get to experience.
게다가 내가 감시당하지 않고
Not to mention
the fact
that there aren't a lot of places I can go
that aren't under constant surveillance.
갈 수 있는 곳 중에 하나야
정부가 날 아주..
The government finds me very...
중요하게 생각하거든
...very valuable.
그건 정부 잘못이 아니지
Well, I can't say
that I blame them.
말도 안돼
You've got to be kidding me.
잠시만
Wait, hold on.
그만 좀 해요
Give me a break.
왜들 이래요? 데이트 하잖아요
밥 먹으러 온거예요
Are you kidding me?
I've got her here. We're having some food.
- 아마추어같긴
- 꼭 그렇게까지 해야겠어?
- Amateur.
- Casey, is that necessary?
겨우 데이트 하는건데
위험해지겠어?
How much trouble can
he get into on a date?
바토스키잖아
It's Bartowski.
슈퍼 컴퓨터 남자친구가
다른 여잘 만나는데도
You're pretty nonchalant about
your supercomputer boyfriend
아무렇지 않은거같네
trying to browse someone
else's network.
난 가짜 여자친구일뿐이야
Well, I am just
his cover girlfriend.
...with your bank of monitors.
이제 그만둬요. 알겠어요?
You get off on this,
don't you?
진짜 여자친구를 가질 자격이 있어
Chuck's entitled to a real one.
케이시 소령, 워커 요원
Major Casey, Agent Walker.
새로운 미션을 알려주겠네
I have the intel
on your new mission.
평소와는 다른 수색이 필요할거야
But it's going to require some
unorthodox reconnaissance.
알고보니 죽은 르플뢰르 박사가
함께 일했던 요원들의
Turns out our deceased doctor,
Guy LeFleur,
암호명이 담긴 목록을
가지고 있었다는군
obtained a list
of CIA code names
for the agents he worked with.
우린 그 목록이 누가
풀크럼 요원인지 알려줄거라 생각하네
We have reason to believe
it's a list
of FULCRUM operatives.
This may be our only chance
누가 변절했는지 알아낼
유일한 기회일지도 몰라
to find the corrupt agents
within our ranks.
잘됐네요
그 목록은 지금 어디있나요?
Great.
And where's the list now?
르플뢰르가 묵었던 월드론 호텔
방에 숨겨져 있는 것 같네
Intel thinks it's hidden
in Guy's hotel room
at the Waldron.
풀크럼이 찾기 전에
우리가 먼저 찾아야하네
We have to get that list
before FULCRUM does.
조용히 인터섹트를 데려가서
떠오르는게 있나 보게
You need to
take the Intersect in
off-the-record
and see if he can flash.
척이 목록이 어디에 숨겨져 있는지
찾아낼 수도 있으니까
Perhaps Chuck can find out
where the list is hidden.
정부에서 통제하고 있는
범죄현장에 침입하란 말씀이세요?
You want us to break into
a government-controlled
crime scene?
It's the FBI.
How hard can it be?
FBI잖아. 별거 아닐걸?
5시 방향에 척이야
Bogie at 5:00.
내가 가볼게
I'll handle this.
지붕에 카메라라뇨?
뭐 때문에요?
Really? A camera on the roof
because of what?
바이모어 위에서 테러리스트가
활동이라도 한대요?
All the terrorist activity
on top of the Buy More?
그래요
케이시가 좀 너무하기도 했어요
Okay, Casey may have been
a little aggressive,
- 하지만 방금 새 임무를 받았어요
- 벌써요?
but we just received our new mission.
- Already?
내일, 르플뢰르가 묵었던
호텔 방에 침입할거예요
Tomorrow we're going to break
into Guy LeFleur's hotel room.
그 방에 박사를 협박하던
풀크럼 요원들 목록이 있는것 같아요
We think he might have a list
of all the FULCRUM agents
that were blackmailing him.
알았어요
Wow. Okay.
내일 마저 얘기해도 될까요?
Can we talk about
this tomorrow?
질이 차에서 기다리고 있어서요
Because I have Jill
그럼요
waiting for me in the car.
Of course.
고마워요
Okay, thanks.
저기요 척
Uh, Chuck...
다 괜찮은거죠?
is everything all right?
네. 네 괜찮아요. 왜요?
Yeah... yeah, I'm fine.
Why do you ask?
스파이 일이예요?
Or is this some spy thing?
정신 감정 뭐 그런거예요?
Some psych evaluation
or something like that?
친구로써 묻는거예요
It's a friend thing.
잘 지내는건지 알고 싶어서요
I just want to make sure
you're okay.
Yeah. Yeah, I'm great.
네. 네, 아주 좋아요
질과 함께 있을땐..
Being with Jill,
is... is...
예전 삶으로 돌아온 것 같아요
It's like having
my old life back, you know?
우리가 위장했던게
싫었다는건 아니지만
And not to bash
on our cover,
진정한 내 모습을 아는 사람과
함께하는게 어떤건지 잊고 있었어요
but I'd forgotten
what it's like to be
with someone who
knows the real me.
제가 지금까지 본 걸로는
정말 좋은 분 같아요
Well, from everything
I've seen,
she seems like a great girl.
조금 덜 봤으면 좋았을텐데요
Well, if you could
see a little less.
척 바토스키 24시간 감시하기
적당히 해주세요
Maybe ease up
on the whole
Chuck Bartowski
24-hour surveillance.
알았어요. 케이시한테 말해둘게요
Yeah, I'll talk to Casey.
사생활 보호 받을 자격 있으니까요
You deserve your
privacy, Chuck.
고마워요
Thank you.
Okay.
갈게요
새라는 이제 감시를
좀 줄이겠다던데요
So Sarah said there's going to be
an easing up
of the Chuck surveillance.
넌 정부 재산이야
You're a government
asset, Chuck.
가끔은 사생활도
버려야 할 때가 있어
(take a back seat)
Sometimes your personal life
has to take a backseat.
뒷자리도 이미 시도해봤어요
(back seat)
We tried the backseat.
차에도 카메라 뒀잖아요
You have a camera
in the car, too.
예전에 헤어진 사람이랑
다시 만날 기회가 얼마나 되겠어요?
Come on, how many...
how many second chances
do you get with
the one who got away?
게다가 질은 내가...
뭔지 알죠
Plus, she already knows
I'm a... you know.
난 내 감정에도 관심없어
I'm not even interested in
my own feelings, Bartowski.
임무에나 집중해
Keep your mind
on the mission.
10분후에 출발할거야
We leave in ten.
안녕 척
안녕하세요 존
Hey, Chuck.
Morning.
캐나다에서 샤니아 트웨인 이후
Canada has just delivered
최고의 선물을 보냈어
(캐나다 가수)
its most delightful gift
since Shania Twain.
Q-36 게임 카피어야
(게임 오디오 비디오 등 복사하는 프로그램)
Behold the Q-36 game copier.
이제 우린 게임 CD 빌려서
Check it out-- now all we
have to do is rent a game,
복사하면 돼. 앞으로
돈 안 써도 되는거야
rip it, and we never have to pay
for our entertainment again.
그래. 빅 마이크가 우리가 어떻게
Yeah, Big Mike's going
to be thrilled
비디오 게임을 팔아먹는지
알면 퍽이나 좋아하겠다
seeing as how we sell
video games.
이게 복사 방지 프로그램을 다 뚫는다니깐
Come on, dude,
this thing can ignore
all forms of copy protection.
뭐든지 다 복사할 수 있어
It can copy anything.
엄청나게 불법인거지
Highly illegal.
뭐가 불법이라는거죠?
What's illegal, gentlemen?
점심시간에 대마초라도
피러 가시는건가요?
Oh. Going to smoke some weed
on your lunch break?
리퍼?
A little reefer?
간자?
(모두 마리화나의 속어)
Ganja?
하역장이 파이브 포 파이팅
(미국의 가수)
I have heard the loading dock
콘서트장 같다는
얘길 들은적이 있어요
is like
a Five for Fighting concert.
아주 격렬하대요
So fierce.
척, 내 사무실에서
잠깐 볼까요?
Chuck, can I see you
in my office, please?
죄송해요 안 되겠어요
Uh, sorry, Emmett, can't.
가봐야해서요
Got to go.
그래요? 어딜요?
Oh, really? Where?
외근 가야해서요
Uh... it's an off-site
install.
시간이 좀 걸릴 것 같아서, 그럼..
It's probably going
to take a while, so...
또 뵈요
See ya.
그니깐 그 가짜 여자친구랑
호텔에 간다는거지?
You're going to a hotel
tonight with your cover girlfriend?
밤새서 임무를 수행할 때는
보통 케이시도 있고
Well, uh, you know, I mean,
if it's any comfort...
overnight missions
normally involve Casey
엄청난 무기들도 많으니까
and a whole lot
of firearms.
전혀 걱정할만한 일은 없을거야
So, nothing romantic about it.
근데 새라는 어때?
So what is this Sarah like?
예뻐?
Is she pretty?
전형적인 이성애자 남자라면
다들 매력적이라고 생각해
Um, well... I could understand
how a typical heterosexual male
might find her aesthetically
pleasing, you know.
만약에 누가 나한테
And if someone
were to ask me,
"Chuck, technically,
objectively,
네 CIA 관리자 새라가
매력적이라고 생각해?"라고 물으면
do you find your CIA
handler Sarah attractive?"
난 이렇게 말할거야
"솔직하게, 객관적으로 말해서.."
Then I might say,
"Technically, objectively...
"..매력적이야"
...Sure."
그래
Uh-huh.
그런데도 네가 맡은 임무들이
And all those
missions you go on,
즐겁거나 로맨틱하지 않다고?
it's not exciting
and romantic?
질, 오해하지마
Look, you got it all wrong.
우리 사이에 섹시고 매력이고
그런건 전혀 없어
There is nothing
about this job
that's glamorous or sexy.
들어가자
All right.
안녕하세요
Hi-oh.
Chuck 2x07
Chuck Versus the Fat lady
재커리 리바이
(척 바토스키 役)
이본느 스트라호브스키
(새라 워커 역 役)
조슈아 고메즈
(모건 그라임즈 役)
라이언 맥파틀린
(캡틴 짱 役)
마크 크리스토퍼 로렌스
(빅 마이크 役)
스캇 크린스키 / 빅 사하이
줄리아 링
새라 랜체스터
(엘리 바토스키 役)
아담 볼드윈
(존 케이시 役)
새라, 정말 옷을 꼭 그렇게..
Was it absolutely necessary
for you to dress up
like a...?
- 에스코트 같다고요?
- 네, 에스코트요
An escort?
- Yeah, yeah, an escort.
그리고 어째서 카마이클이
당신을 나하고 섹스하자고..
And why exactly is Mr. Carmichael
paying you to have sex with me...
- 아니 카마이클이랑요
- 월드론 호텔은 사업가들의
...him?
The Waldron is notorious
밀회장소로 유명해요
for its high-end businessmen
and their trysts.
이게 우리 위장이니깐
제대로 해요
It's our cover, so sell it.
저 여자 얼마에 샀을까?
Wonder how much
that costs?
보안 카메라 연결됐어
I've got the security feed.
FBI에서 기의 방을
제대로 통제하고 있는것 같군
It looks like the FBI
has Guy's room on lockdown.
들어가기전에 승인 받을 것 없이
We won't be asking
permission before we slip in.
환기구를 통해서 들어가야겠어
We'll just enter through
the ventilation system.
저기, 저기요
Hey, hey...
이거 얼마나 걸려요?
how long is this
going to take?
왜 그래, 바토스키
데이트라도 있어?
What's the matter,
Bartowski, you got a date?
네 있어요
Actually, yes.
괜찮아요?
Ow!
You okay?
그냥 전화해서 우리가
간다고 대놓고 알려주지 그래?
Why don't you just call ahead
and let them know we're coming?
- 죄송해요
- 멍청한 놈
Sorry.
Idiot.
집에 언제쯤 갈 수 있나
궁금해서 그랬어요
I'm just trying to figure out
what time I'm going to be home.
계산해봐요
Well, just do
the cover math.
사업가가 창녀랑 섹스하는데
시간이 얼마나 걸리겠어요?
How long would it take
for a businessman
to have sex
with a prostitute?
핸드폰 성가셔죽겠네
Stupid phone.
여보세요?
새라, 우리가 섹스하는데
한 시간 이상 걸릴 것 같아요?
Hello?
Sarah, you think
this shouldn't take us
more than an hour to have sex
from start to finish?
네
Uh-huh.
그럼...
And...
시작해요
begin.
저기요 저, 저 어떻게하죠?
What... what am I...
What am I doing wrong here?
엉덩이를 조금만 왼쪽으로 움직여봐요
Well, just move your hips
a little to the left.
네.. 알았어요
Okay... okay.
이거 제가
생각했던것보다 더 힘든데요
This is way more exhausting
than I thought it would be.
그럼 그냥 해낼 수 있을줄 알았어요?
Well, we can't
just race right through it.
무릎 안 아파요?
Your knees aren't hurting?
이런거 배우는 학교라도 다닌거예요?
What, did you go to a school
to learn how to do this?
안녕하세요?
Hey, how are you?
안녕하세요, 에밋
Hello, Emmett.
스낵 가지러 잠깐 온 거예요
I was just coming in here
to get a snack.
앉아보세요
Oh, you do not need a snack.
Please.
Okay.
네
모건, 잠시동안 바이모어가
국가라고 상상해보세요
Morgan, I want you
to imagine, for a moment,
that Buy More is a country.
바이모리아요
Ah, BuyMoria.
Yes.
네
어떻게 알았어요?
How did you know that?
지난 몇 년간 생각해왔거든요
I've thought about it for years.
잘됐네요
This is fantastic.
모든 직원들이 이 훌륭한 나라를
구성하는 주(州)들이라고 상상해보세요
Now, imagine that
all its employees
are the states that make up
this great nation.
네. 그건 할 수 있겠네요
Yeah, I can dig it.
그 중 하나의 주(州)가
나라를 떠나려 하고 있어요
And, if you will,
one of these states
is looking to secede
from the union.
척이요
Chuck.
Whoa.
에밋, 잠시만요
지금 바이모리아에 대한
Okay, wait a minute.
척의 애국심을 의심하시는거예요?
말도 안돼요
You're questioning
Chuck's patriotism
towards BuyMoria? No.
척은 항상 어딜 그렇게 가는거예요?
Where does he go
all the time?
척이 간다던 외근 영수증은 못 봤는데요
I don't see receipts for all
the off-site installs he does.
대체 뭐에 중독된거죠, 모건?
What is he into, Morgan?
각성제? 본드?
Uppers? Glue?
싱글맘?
A baby mama?
이봐요. 당신 미쳤어요?
Dude, you are out of your mind.
그럴지도 모르죠
Maybe I am.
당신 정보를 캐내느라
좀 미친것 같기도 하네요
Maybe I'm so far out of my mind
that I've gotten myself
all crawled up inside of yours.
한번 볼까요
Let's see.
이런
Oh.
이 정도면 바이모리아에서
추방당할 충분한 이유가 될 것 같은데요
This could be grounds
for deportation
from BuyMoria.
그러시진 않겠죠
You wouldn't.
날 도와줘요, 모건
Help me, Morgan.
내가 척을 도울수 있게
도와줘요
Help me help Chuck.
척은 우리 도움 필요 없어요
Chuck doesn't need our help.
걔가 뭐라던 신경 안써
Don't matter what she said.
오후 보초 근무는 지겨워
Afternoon guard
duty is boring.
여기
Here.
거기서 뭐해요?
What are you doing up there?
도와줘요!
Help!
쉿! FBI가 멍청하긴 하지만
귀머거리는 아니야
Shh! It's the FBI.
They're dumb,
not deaf.
고마워요
Thanks.
미안해요
Sorry.
저기요 저기요
Hey. Hey.
그러더니 나보고
헤어지자는거 있지
And then she
shoves him in the pool.
I swear, if it wasn't
for the Xanax,
she would have
ripped his...
왔어?
Hey, man.
오늘은 안 올줄 알았는데
I didn't expect
to see you today.
네가 이게 필요할 땐
절대 쉬면 안 되지
Well, never a day off
when you need it.
Ow!
Shh! Shh! Shh!
"조용히"라는 단어에 내가
모르는 다른 뜻도 있나?
Does the word "silent" have
a different meaning in geek
케이시, 미안해요
진동인줄 알았어요
that I'm not aware of?
- Look, I'm sorry.
I thought it was on vibrate.
그래도 목록은 얻었잖아요
At least I got the list.
베니스 퍼즐 상자예요
It's a Venetian Puzzle Box.
르네상스 향신료와 함께 유명했었죠
Very popular with
Renaissance spies.
잠겼어요
It's locked.
Hey-- beh, beh, beh.
뛰고 점프하고 사람들 쏘는건
새라와 케이시 몫이지만
The running, jumping, shooting
people part of the job,
이 퍼즐은, 제 몫이예요
that's all you guys.
But the puzzles, that's all me.
1에서 12까지 연속으로
이어지는 것 같지만
I think it would be
numerals one through
12 in a row.
이런 상자들은
복잡한 피보나치 수열을 사용해요
But these boxes used
a complicated
Fibonacci sequence.
안에 뭐가 들었나 볼까요
Let's see what we got.
케이시, 가스야!
Oh, Casey, gas!
- 장비 가지고 금방 올게!
- 이게 뭐예요?
Be right back with a containment unit.
- Well, is it off?!
- 뭐냐고요!
- 옷 벗어요!
Get it off me!
Take your clothes off!
샤워해야해요, 서둘러요!
Get in the shower now, quick!
Off! Get it off!
- 빨리 바지 벗어요!
- 벗고 있잖아요!
Pants off, come on!
I'm trying!
서둘러요!
Hurry up!
빨리 들어와요
Get in, get
in, get in.
차가워요!
너무 너무 너무 차가워요!
Oh, cold! So-so-so cold!
비누로 빨리 씻어요!
Use the soap!
Wash it!
Oh! Oh!
오 미안해요! 미안해요!
Get the--
Oh, sorry, sorry!
제가 그게 일부러 그런게 아니고..
I'm trying to--
I'm not trying to...!
얼굴 씻어요
Wash your face properly.
비누 맛이 나요
Tastes like soap!
머리도 씻어요
In your hair.
Oh! Oh, God.
문 열어줘요
케이시일거예요
Get the door. That's Casey.
낭비할 시간 없어요
빨리요
We have no time
to waste; quick.
질?
Jill.
척 / 네가 어떻게..
Chuck.
How'd you...
벨보이가 알려줬어
The bellman sent me
to your room.
이럴 줄 알았어
I knew it.
질, 잠시만!
네가 생각하는 그런거 아니야!
Jill, wait!
Wait, wait! It's
not what you think!
질, 제발!
Jill, please!
나 지금 죽어가는지도 몰라!
I could be dying!
이거 얼마나 걸려요?
How long... how long
does this thing take?
어떻게 질이
딱 그 순간에 들어올수가 있죠?
How-how does Jill pick that
exact moment to walk in on us?
아니, 이럴수가 있어요?
I mean, what-what-
what are the odds?
이거 해독제도 주는거예요?
Does-does this, does this
give us the antidote?
저 지금 숨이 막히는 것 같아서요
Because I think
I feel my throat
is closing up on me right now.
뭐래요?
What is it?
뭐래요, 살 뜯어먹는 박테리아?
탄저균이래요?
What is it,
flesh-eating bacteria
or anthrax?
저 죽게되나요?
Am I gonna die?
아니. 얼음 넣어서
길거리에서 애들한테 팔아
Nope.
But you can add ice
and give it to little kids
to sell on street corners.
I knew it.
이럴 줄 알았어
마약인가봐요
Drugs.
과일 펀치야 멍청아
It's powdered fruit punch,
dumb ass.
Wait...
잠시만요
So not only
그럼 풀크럼 요원 목록도 못 얻고
did we not get
the FULCRUM list,
다른 여자랑 홀딱 벗고
펀치로 샤워하는 장면을
but Jill's never gonna speak to
me again because she caught me
들켰다고 질이 다신
저랑 얘기도 안할거란거예요?
naked, rinsing off fruit punch
with another woman?
스파이라면 항상 생기는 문제지
Common spy problem.
Really?
그래요?
I don't know what to tell you.
뭘 말씀드려야할지 모르겠네요
전 아무것도 모르는데요
I don't know anything.
모르긴요, 레스터
Oh, of course you do, Lester.
찰스랑 수년간 가깝게 지냈다면서요
You've worked
very closely with Charles
for years.
제가 척과의 사이에 대해서
조금 과장해서 말한 것 같기도해요
Perhaps I've overstated
the nature of our relationship.
저희 그렇게 친하진 않거든요
We don't socialize much.
사실 여러번 기분 나쁜일도 있었고요
In fact, I've felt slighted
on more than one occasion.
오 잘됐네요
Oh, good.
그렇다면 고자질하는데에
아무런 문제가 없겠어요
Then you won't have a problem
ratting him out.
양심에 찔려서 그러는게 아니예요
I have no ethical dilemma.
정말 아무것도 모른다고요!
I meant I just don't
know anything!
그럼 누가 아는데요!
Then who does?!
제프요!
제프한테 물어보세요
Jeff!
I would ask Jeff.
전 밀고는 안해요
I don't rat.
그게 저희 엄마가 감옥에서
가르쳐주신 유일한 거예요
Only thing
my mother
taught me from
the joint.
대답을 원하면
"인준"한테 물어보세요
You want answers,
talk to the Injun.
"Injun" is a highly
derogatory term
"인준"은 아메리카 인디언들한테
아주 모욕적인 말이야
인도 사람이 아니고! 이 바보야!
referring to
Native Americans,
not East Indians,
you cretin!
삽들고 빨리 움직여
Grab a shiv and make your move.
우리 빨리 도망가야해요
얘 감옥 모드에 빠졌어요
We should run now.
He's in "prison mode."
닥쳐요
Shut up.
I guess I haven't
made myself clear.
내가 확실하게 말을 안 한 모양인데
You both host an
unsanctioned card game
두 사람 모두 휴게실에서
카드게임을 열었더군요
in this break room.
바토스키에 대해서 알려주면
You give me something
on Bartowski
밤에 포커치는거 모른척 할게요
or no more poker night.
척은 여자친굴 두고 바람펴요
Chuck's cheating on his lady.
며칠 전에 멋있고 세련된
레스토랑에서
Yeah, we saw him and
this brunette bird
leaving some fancy,
real-silverware joint
어떤 갈색 머리 여자랑
떠나는걸 봤어요
a couple of
nights ago.
제 취향만큼 가슴이
풍만하진 않더라고요
She's not as well-endowed
as I would like.
거짓말하고있네
Come on.
이름이 뭐예요?
What's her name?
누구예요?
Who is she?
포커는 끝났네
No more poker
모건!
No...
Morgan!
모건을 캐보세요
You got to break Morgan.
척이 걔한테는 다 얘기해요
Chuck tells him everything.
걔 턱수염에 비밀을 담고 살아요
His beard holds so many secrets.
Morgan.
모건
안녕, 질
Hey, Jill.
나야 또 척이야
It's-It's me again-- Chuck.
행운의 4번째 메시지야
Lucky message number four.
있지. 네가 전화 다시
안 해주는거, 나 다 이해해
Listen, I just wanted to say,
I totally understand why
you're not calling me back.
나도 네 입장이었으면
너처럼 생각했을거야
Because, look,
if I saw what you saw,
then I'd be thinking
what you're thinking, you know.
그렇다고 내가 네 생각을 안다는건 아니고
Not that I presume to know
what you're thinking.
네가 본게 네가 생각하는거라고
생각하는 논리적인 추론의 결과야
It's just a logical deduction
to think what you saw would be
what you think, if that's
in fact what you're thinking.
Actually, I can explain
a lot better than that,
네가 나한테 전화 좀 해주면
나 더 잘 설명할 수 있어
if you just call me back.
네가 편한 시간에
전화해줘. 끊을게
Please.
At your earliest convenience.
Bye.
그라임즈
Grimes.
너 에밋한테 뭐든지 말 좀 해줘
You got to give Milbarge
something, man.
If you don't,
안 그러면 앞으로
매주 하는 포커를 못하게 하겠대
he's not gonna let us
have our weekly poker game.
그래. 우릴 위해서가 아니라
Yeah, don't do it
for us, Morgan.
바이모리아를 위해서 그렇게 해줘
Do it for BuyMoria.
그래요, 그라임즈
So, Grimes,
오늘 아침의 대화에 대해서
좀 더 생각해봤나요?
have you thought any more
about our chat this morning?
내가 바이모리아를 돕는걸
도울 준비가 됐나요?
Are you ready to help me
help BuyMoria?
Yeah, okay, Emmett.
네, 됐어요 에밋
얘기할게요
Okay.
척이 외근간다고 하고
어딜 가는지 알고 싶다는거죠?
You want to know where Chuck
goes on these... service calls?
네 맞아요
Yes, please.
방문해서 컴퓨터와
컴퓨터 관련 소프트웨어를 고쳐요
He goes and he
fixes computers
and computer-
related software.
왜 보호하는거죠?
Why do you protect him?
약점 잡힌거라도 있어요?
What does that Charles
have over you?
23년간의 우정이랄까요
Um, 23 years
of best friendship.
그만해요
Oh, please.
I know everything
전 모든걸 알고 있지만
절대 말씀 드리지 않을거예요
there is to know
about the man, but
you're not gonna hear it
from me. And if you're
약점을 찾고 계신거라면,
드릴 말씀이 없네요
looking for dirt,
well, nothing to say,
왜냐하면 척은 제가 아는
제일 정직한 사람이거든요
dude, 'cause
Chuck Bartowski
is the straightest
shooter I know.
Really?
그래요? / 네
That's right.
정직함의 기준이 신기하네요
You have a bizarre sense
of straightest.
그 친구가 양다리를 걸치는데도 말이죠
Since your besty
has two girlfriends.
What are you talking about?
무슨 소리예요?
I mean, isn't Bartowski's bimbo
a blonde?
바토스키 여자친구는 금발 아닌가요?
새라가 자연 금발인지는 모르겠네요
I don't know if Sarah's
a natural blonde.
그런 질문은 좀 실례잖아요
I mean, it's kind of
impolite to ask, you know.
세상에 질이잖아
Oh, my God, it's Jill.
고마워요
이름은 몰랐는데 말이죠
Thank you.
I didn't know its name.
척의 대학 시절 여자친구예요
That's, that's Chuck's
old college girlfriend.
다시 한번 고마워요
Thank you again.
정보가 넘치네요
You're a font
of information.
알고 있던것보다
두 배는 더 알게됐어요
Twice the intelligence
I had before.
어떻게 나한테 얘길 안했지?
How could he
not have told me?
아참 이제부턴
포커 게임 해도 돼요
Oh, you can have
your poker game now.
그리고 걱정하지 마세요
And do not worry.
당신이 고자질했다고
척한테 안 이를게요
I will not tell Bartowski
that his best buddy
was the weak link.
Cheers.
힘내요
미안해
Sorry. Okay.
질, 고마워
Jill, thank you,
고마워, 이렇게 여기까지
와줘서 고마워
thank you, thank you so much
for-for coming, Jill.
정말 고마워
I appreciate it.
내가 본게 사실이 아니라고
해명할 시간 3초 줄게
You have three seconds
to convince me
what I saw wasn't
what I saw.
그게 좀 힘들어
That's gonna be a little tough,
내가 너한테 그 얘길 하려면
너한테 기밀 정보까지 얘기 해야 하는데..
because I can't
get into specifics
without you having
to know, like,
really high-level,
top-secret government...
We broke into Guy's room
trying to find
우리가 뭘 좀 찾으려고
기의 호텔방을 침입했는데
some of his research,
and we found
상자를 찾아서 열어봤더니
어떤 액체가 우리한테 뿌려진거야
this box, but when we opened it,
it sprayed this stuff
all over Sarah and I,
so when you saw the two of us in
네가 왔을 때 우린 그 액체가
독인줄 알고 씻는 중이었던건데
our underpants what you
really saw was two people
알고보니깐 독이 아니고
과일 펀치더라고
trying to wash off
what we thought was poison but
알겠지? 봐 간단하잖아
내 말 믿지?
really turned out to be
powdered fruit punch.
See? There. Simple.
Do you believe me?
What kind of fruit punch?
무슨 과일 펀치였어?
그래, 이젠 날 가지고 노는구나
Okay, now you're just
messing with me.
아니야, 아냐 척
너 믿어
No, no. Chuck, I believe you.
정말? 왜냐하면
Really? Becau--
내가 생각해도
정말 황당한 얘기라서
I-I was listening to
what I just said right now,
and I sounded
completely ridiculous.
기 씨는 편집증이 심했어
Guy was crazy paranoid.
퍼즐을 풀지 않고선
메일 하나도 못 읽어볼걸
You couldn't open an e-mail
without solving a puzzle first.
뭔가 중요한게 있었다면
분명 숨겨뒀을거야
If he cared about something,
he would have hidden it.
그니까 그 과일 펀치도
중요한 단서일수도 있어
Maybe the fruit punch
was a clue.
We have to go somewhere.
어디 좀 가자
근데 그 전에,
안대 쓰는거 좋아해?
But before we do,
how do you feel
about blindfolds?
You brought her here?
여길 데려와?
Um...
그게..
아무나 초대할 수 있으면
그게 비밀 장소야?
Bartowski, it's not
a secret location
if you invite people over.
알아요, 하지만 기의 퍼즐에
대해 알고 있길래요
Okay, but Jill here,
Jill knows about Guy's puzzles.
방금 그 호텔방에서
FBI요원 둘이 살해된채 발견됐어
They just found two dead FBI
agents in LaFleur's room.
그니까 지금은 여자친구랑
뭐하고 놀까 고민할 시간이 없다고
Now's not the time to be planning
game night with your girlfriend.
질, 나한테 해줬던 과일 펀치가
단서란 얘기 다시 한번 해줘
Jill, would you please
tell them what you told me,
about how the fruit punch
might actually be a clue.
기의 편집증은 이상할 정도였어요
Guy's paranoia manifested
itself in obscure ways:
문학작품에서 따오거나
수학 증명도 있었고
odd literary references,
mathematical proofs.
컴퓨터에 접속하려면
The log-on for
his computer was
보건의 시에서 무작위로
선택한 단어를 쳐야했어요
a randomly selected word
from a piece of Vogon poetry.
그래서, 과일 펀치가
무슨 뜻인것 같아?
So what do you think
the fruit punch might mean?
어떤 종류의 과일 펀치였어요?
What kind of fruit
punch was it?
Uh, I guess,
traditional fruit punch.
아마 평범한 과일 펀치겠죠
아마라고요?
You guess?
정확한 구성비를 알아야해요
Please tell me
you got the exact formula.
알겠어요. 그럼
여기 질량 분석기 있나요?
Okay, um,
is there a mass spectrometer
around?
케이시. 하나 갖다줘요
Casey, get the spectrometer.
우리 그런거 있어요?
Do we have one of those?
뭐 때문에 쟤가 그렇게
빠져있는지 알겠는데?
I can see what the boy
sees in her, huh?
이제 아까 그 물질의 화학 구성과
Now we compare the crystalline
powder's chemical composition
다른 펀치의 화학 구성과 비교할거예요
with a list of
known products.
루틴 라즈베리 Hi-C 맛이래요
It's, um, it's
Rootin' Raspberry-flavored Hi-C.
루틴 라즈베리라면
Rootin' Raspberry?
풋볼 팀이나 치어리더랑
관련된걸까요?
Maybe... Maybe it has something
to do with a football team
or cheerleaders?
공해가 아닐까요?
(공해 : international waters = high sea)
What about international waters?
High seas.
아 공해요
그거 정말 좋은 생각이네요
That's good.
잠시만요
이건 뮤직박스잖아요
Wait, guys, guys,
this is a music box.
It's a music box.
공해(High sea)의 SEA가 아니고
It's not high sea-- S-E-A.
악보에 있는
3옥타브 도(High C)인거예요
It's high "C," like
a musical note-- high "C."
조율관은 왜 꼭
필요할 때 없는거예요?
Where's a pitch pipe
when you need one?
Hey! What?
- 방금 뭐예요?
- 성가대원이었어
Choir boy.
왜? 나도 하기 싫었다고
What? I wasn't hatched.
Ha-ha-ha!
이것 좀 봐요!
Check it out!
오페라 글라스네
Those are opera glasses.
Oh! No...
아니 오페라 글라스가 아니야
actually, they're not.
이건 정말 정교한 잠금장치의 열쇠예요
Um, this is a key.
A key to a very super secret
lock box.
독립전쟁 때 컬퍼링에서
정보를 교환할 때 쓰던거예요
The Culper Ring used to use
stuff like that to pass
information during the
Revolutionary War days.
Wow, Chuck, that's impressive.
척, 대단하다
그래, 잘했어 똘똘아
Yeah, nice going there, brainiac.
근데 그렇게 실실거리기전에
But before you go getting
all full of yourself--
if this is the key,
where's the lock?
이게 열쇠라면
잠금장치는 어딨는데?
케이시, 제대로 된 질문은요
"오페라는 어디있지?"
The question, my dear Casey is:
Where's the opera?
You're not concerned
to involve a civilian
이런 기밀 작전에 민간인이
연관됐는데 신경 안 쓰여?
in a covert government
investigation?
Ah, the girl's
personal knowledge
그 여자가 아는게 우리한테
도움이 되잖아
of Guy LaFleur makes
her of use to us.
바토스키랑 만나는 여자라서
질투하는거 아냐?
You sure you're not
just jealous
Bartowski's found himself
a new piece of asset?
이 멍청한 놈은 어딜 가있는거야
Now where is that doofus?
기 씨는 오페라를 좋아했어
여기가 기씨네 가족 좌석이야
Guy loved the opera.
Here's his family's box.
와 나쁘지 않은데
Whoa! Not bad.
여기서보면 정말 잘 보이겠어
You really feel like you're on
top of the action.
뭘 찾아야하는지 어떻게 알아?
How do you know what
you're looking for?
이 열쇠 끝 부분하고
맞는 걸 찾으면 되지
Oh, well...
it'll match
the end of this key.
뭔가...
You know, something...
something...
뭔가..
...like this.
이렇게 생긴거
뭐가 있나 볼까?
Shall we see what we got?
빙고
Bingo.
찾았어요!
Hey, we got it!
금방 나갈거예요, 아시겠죠?
Mr. Kolfi, we'll be out
of your hair
시간이 없어요
리허설 중이었단 말입니다
in a minute, okay?
I don't have a minute.
We are trying to rehearse.
정말 금방이면
곧 끝날거예요
This is a quick,
quick, quick minute.
정부 기관 일이라서요
You know, government stuff.
조심해요
Watch out.
케이시, 이거 폭탄이야
Casey, that's a bomb.
자 리허설은 끝났어요
밖으로 나가세요!
All right, rehearsal's over.
Everyone out of here!
Come on, Chuck, let's go!
We gotta go!
가요, 척
나가야해요
Wait!
This doesn't make any sense.
잠시만! 이건 말이 안돼
Guy wanted to help people,
not hurt them.
기는 사람들을 돕길 원했지
해치려고 한 적은 없었어
This isn't a bomb,
this is a clue.
폭탄이 아니고
단서일거야
Jill, if it looks like a bomb
질, 폭탄같이 생기고, 똑딱거리면
보통은 다 폭탄이예요
and it ticks like a bomb,
then generally it's a bomb.
No, this is a puzzle we need to
solve before the timer runs out.
아니예요. 시간이 지나기전에
이 퍼즐을 풀어야해요
And what if you're wrong?
That doesn't happen.
그게 아니라면요?
그럴리 없어요
Look, it's a music thing.
What's the opera?
음악과 관련된거잖아
이 오페라 제목이 뭐야?
Verdi's La Traviata.
베르디의 라 트라비아타
Well, how does that go?
음이 어떻게 돼?
너 바이올린 켤 줄 알지? / 응
You play violin, right?
- Mm-hmm.
Your dad made you play
the flute.
너 네 아버지때문에
플룻 배웠었지
Let's not bring that up.
그 얘긴 하지 말자
어서요 어서
빨리 나와요!
Come on. Come on.
Get 'em all out!
All of 'em!
Go, go!
빨리! 나가요 나가!
It's not happening.
Let's go.
Chuck, come on!
그만해요. 어서 가요
척 빨리요!
Look, look, Jill has yet
to be wrong, okay?
새라, 질 얘기가
틀렸는지 아직은 모르잖아요
She says it's not a bomb,
I believe her.
폭탄이 아닐거라잖아요
난 그 말 믿어요
Sir, we're sealing
this place off.
It's a flash drive.
This must be it.
이건 플래쉬 드라이브예요
틀림없어요
That's how we
do that, huh?
우리가 해낸거죠?
Jill, it was all you.
질, 네가 해낸거야
No, you.
It was all you.
아니야 네가 한거지
Okay, all right, all right.
I love love.
사랑이구만
The flash drive containing
Guy's list is encrypted
그 플래쉬 드라이브는 512비트
AES 사이퍼를 이용해서 암호화 되어있었네
using a 512-bit AES cipher.
Right now, the computer is
trying every possible key
지금 컴퓨터가 모든 가능한
암호는 대입하고 있어
against the encrypted data.
When it finds a match,
we'll have the identity
해독하는 즉시 기와 접촉하던
of every FULCRUM agent
with whom Guy was in contact.
모든 풀크럼요원들의 신원을
파악 할 수 있게 될거야
How long will
that take?
얼마나 걸릴까요?
Could be hours,
could be days.
몇 시간이 될 수도
몇 일이 될 수도 있네
Excellent work, you two.
둘 다 수고 많았네
Please thank the asset
for his service.
척에게도 수고했다고 전해주게
Where is Chuck
right now?
그러고보니, 척은 어디있나?
My guess would be rounding
second base.
아마 재미보고 있겠죠
You were
brilliant tonight.
오늘 정말 대단했어
No, you.
네가 대단했지
Mm-mm, all you.
아니야 다 네덕이야
안돼 안돼 안돼 난 못해
Mm-mm-mm! No, no, no, I can't,
I can't, I can't do this.
You don't have to do a thing.
It's gonna be all me.
넌 아무것도 안해도돼
내가 다 할거니까
I... mm, that's very
gracious of you,
정말 정말 고맙지만
but no, that's not
what I'm saying.
내 말은 그게 아니야
I mean, I can't do this.
이렇게는 못하겠다고
I can't, I can't do this.
안돼 못해 이렇게는 안돼
Hey, come here.
질, 이리 와봐
Come here.
Come here. Look...
어서 어서
내일 바이모어에서 만나
Buy More. Tomorrow.
What time?
Take the latent heat
of aquatic fusion...
언제?
물의 숨은열에서..
Is that in calories per gram?
Kcal/g 단위로? / 물론이지
Of course.
And then subtract the atomic
number of thulium.
거기에 툴륨의 원자번호를 빼
Got it?
Mm-hmm.
알았지?
응
Okay, I'll see you then.
그래, 내일 보자
Nerd code.
똘똘이들 암호라 이거지
Hm.
Hey, hey, buddy,
안녕 모건
에밋한테 내 핑계 좀 잘 대줘
listen, I need you to cover
for me with Emmett today.
Gotta cut out early.
오늘 일찍 퇴근해야해
I see-- big night
with the lady, huh?
그래, 데이트라도 있는 모양이지?
Actually, uh, yeah.
응 맞아
We're sneaking off for a
little romantic getaway.
어디 여행가기로 했거든
Oh, how sweet.
좋겠네
So you and Sarah are taking
a little trip together, huh?
너랑 새라랑 둘이서 여행가는구나?
Yeah, we're, uh...
응, 우리 둘이서...
Just save it, Pinocchio.
I know you're seeing Jill.
그만해, 피노키오
질이랑 만나는거 다 알아
You what? You... How?
안다고? 뭐? 어떻게?
How do you--
you know about Jill?
네가 그걸 어떻게 알아?
Apparently, I'm the last one
to know, too.
사실 난 제일 늦게 안거야
Milbarge knows about it.
심지어 에밋까지 알고있더라
This is Jill.
네가 질 잊는거 도와주는데
몇 달이나 걸렸다고
I spent months helping you
get over her.
Look, Chuck, we're best friends,
척, 우린 제일 친한 친구잖아
but if you're not telling me
about this, what else
근데 이런 얘길 안해주다니
또 나한테 말 안한거 있어?
aren't you telling me?
Morgan, I'm so sorry, buddy.
모건, 정말 미안해
I really am.
And-And trust me, there is so much
진심이야
나도 정말 너한테
that I wish
that I could tell you,
말해주고 싶지만
하지만 그럴수가 없어
but I, you know, can't.
Dude, you've never lied
to me before.
너 나한테
거짓말 한적 없었잖아
Exactly, so just trust
my judgment on this, okay?
그래, 그니까 이번 일엔
날 좀 믿어줘, 알았지?
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry. I gotta go.
정말 미안해
진심이야. 나 가봐야겠어
잘 얘기해줄거지?
Can you cover me?
Of course, I can cover
for you, man,
물론이지. 내가 알아서 할게
because we're best friends
왜냐하면 우린 친한 친구 사이고
그런 사이끼린 서로를 위해서
and that's what
best friends do--
they lie for each other.
거짓말도 해주잖아
서로에게 거짓말하는게 아니고
But they don't lie
to each other,
that's all.
Got it.
알겠어
Trust me.
And thank you, thank you.
날 믿어
그리고 정말 고마워
I'm gonna grab some
turkey jerky inside.
난 가서 터키 저키 좀 사올게
필요한거 있어?
Do you want anything?
Uh, a water
and some Gummi Bears.
물이랑 구미 베어
(곰 모양 젤리)
Okay, coming right up.
알았어 금방 올게
Have you heard from Chuck?
척한테 소식 없어?
No. I'll do a GPS search
on his watch.
응. 시계에 붙여논 GPS 추적해볼게
Little twerp's gone off grid.
멍청이가 또 사라졌어
Hey, no Gummi Bears,
so I hope you like sour...
질, 구미 베어가 없길래 그냥..
Chuck, help!
척 살려줘!
Jill!
- 질!
- 멈춰서
That's close enough.
You have something
that belongs to me.
당신이 내 물건을 갖고 있어
What? No. This?
뭐? 아니야
이거?
No, no, no. See, I paid--
아니야 이건 내거야
내가 내 돈주고 산거라고
I paid for this.
But you can have it.
Why don't you just
let the girl go
하지만 원한다면 가져가
여자는 그냥 놓아주고
and then you can tell me
what it is exactly
네가 잃어버린게 뭔지 말해봐
that you've lost, then maybe
I can help you find it?
내가 도울 수 있을지도 모르잖아?
Bring me LaFleur's list
or the girl dies.
르플뢰르의 목록을 가져와
아님 이 여잔 죽어
Opera House.
자정까지 오페라 하우스로 와
Midnight.
They took her!
The hell you been?
- 그 사람들이 질을 납치했어요!
- 대체 어딨었어?
You deliberately went off grid.
Some guy just took Jill!
- 일부러 도망친거지
- 질이 납치됐다고요!
He said if I didn't bring him
Guy's list of
그 목록을 안 가져오면
질을 죽이겠대요
FULCRUM agents,
he's gonna kill her.
That's not gonna happen.
Yeah, of course not.
- 그런 일은 없을거야
- 당연하죠
I'm gonna bring him the list,
and I'm gonna get her back!
당장 그 목록 갖다주고
질을 데려올거예요
No, you're not.
아니, 그렇게는 안돼
어떻게 되든 질은 죽게될거야
They'll kill her either way.
네? 안돼요
그럴순 없어요
What? No.
That can't happen.
제발요 케이시
제발 도와줘요
Please, Casey,
will you please help me?
No.
안돼. 워싱턴에 보고해야겠어
I gotta call Washington
and report it.
넌 여기서 꼼짝말고 있어
You stay right here.
Don't move.
사고는 충분히 쳤으니까
You've done
enough damage already.
장군님, 문제가 생겼습니다
General,
we have a situation.
안돼! 멈춰서!
Stop!
- 워커! 쏴!
- 꼼짝마! 움직이지 마요
Walker, shoot him!
Chuck, freeze!
Don't.
당신이 그걸 가져가면
난 쏠 수 밖에 없어요
If you try to take that,
I have to stop you.
Please, let me go!
제발 그냥 보내주세요
이건 반역이야, 바토스키
This is treason, Bartowski.
제발 그냥 보내주세요
Please, just let me go.
Shoot him, Walker.
어서 쏴, 워커
쏴 버리라고!
Shoot him
in the knee.
I'm sorry.
미안해요
I have to.
어쩔수 없어요
It's Jill.
질이 위험해요
You could've
shot him.
총을 쐈어야지
인터섹트잖아
He's the Intersect.
그게 다야?
Is that all he is?
무릎을 쏴도 되는거였잖아
You could've at least
kneecapped him.
추적중이야
시내로 향하고 있어
I have a trace on Chuck.
He's heading downtown.
차 준비해, 난 총 꺼내올게
You get the car,
I'll get the guns.
Jill!
질!
척!
Chuck.
그런건 집어치우고
거래나 시작하지
Can we dispense
with the pillow talk
and just do this?
그래 좋아. 그렇게 해
Yeah, yeah,
okay, okay.
- 질을 놔줘
- 당장은 안되지
Let her go.
Not so fast.
내 패를 봤으니
네 패를 보여줘야지
You've seen mine,
now show me yours.
That's fine, but first I need to
know that she's gonna be safe.
알았어. 하지만 그 전에
질부터 놔줘
그렇게는 안되지
That's not how this works.
목록을 내놔. 아님
너희 둘 다 쏴버릴테니까
You hand over the list,
or I shoot you both.
그것도 그렇게는 안되지
That's not how
this works either!
Go wait in the car, Chuck.
차에 가서 기다려, 척
가긴 어딜 가
Don't move, Chuck.
거기서 꼼짝말고 있어
Stay right where you are.
저쪽에 널 겨냥 중인
저격수가 있어
I've got a sharpshooter
trained on you.
Now I have the sniper.
이젠 나한테 저격수가 생겼네
그래도 여전히 내가 유리해
I-I still have the advantage.
목록을 내놔
안 그러면 척을 쏘겠어
Somebody give me the list,
or I shoot Chuck.
그래. 그냥 확 쏴버려
Yeah, go ahead
and shoot him.
안 그래도 내가 직접 쏴버릴까 싶었거든
You know, I was thinking about
shooting him myself.
잘 생각했어요
네? 뭐라고요?
That's a great--
Why would you-- What, what?!
정신 나갔어요?
What are you, crazy?!
이건 어때요?
아무도 척을 안 쏘는건요?
How about nobody,
how about nobody shoots Chuck?!
난 새라가 아니야, 척
I'm not Sarah, Chuck.
Give him that list,
네가 목록을 넘기면
내가 네 불쌍한 인생을 끝내주지
and I will end your miserable
existence. It's your choice.
네가 선택해
이 여잘 쏘는게 더 나을까?
Would you rather
I shoot the girl?
그러지 마요. 차라리 날 쏴요
Please don't.
I would rather you not shoot
총은 나한테 겨누라고요
the girl-- just point
the gun back at me, please.
안돼!
No!
아니 그러지말고
여자를 쏴
No, go ahead, shoot the girl.
상황에 따라서는
부수적인 피해도 생기기 마련이니까
Some situations,
collateral damage
is unavoidable.
아니요 그렇지 않아요
No.
It's always avoidable.
이봐요, 내가 갖고 있어요
나한테 있어요
Look, I have it, okay?
Here it is.
- 여기요. 여기안에 있어요
- 바토스키!
Right here, here's the list.
- Bartowski!
Look, you got
a better plan?
더 좋은 생각 있어요?
왜냐하면 난 부수적인
피해는 원치 않거든요
'Cause I'm not okay with
collateral damage right now.
자 받아요
Here you go.
풀크럼 요원 목록이예요
Here's your list of all
the FULCRUM agents.
케이시, 우리가
정부에 누굴 심어뒀는지
Well, Mr. Casey,
FULCRUM would rather
당신들이 모르는 편이 더 좋거든
you not know who we have
inside government.
- 쇼는 계속 되어야해
- 지금이야, 새라!
Show must go on.
Now, Sarah!
질, 괜찮아 이젠 괜찮아
정말 미안해
Okay. Hey, hey. You're okay.
이제 갔어. 떠났어
이젠 괜찮아
You're okay...
미안해
Oh, I'm so sorry.
정말 미안해
괜찮아?
I'm so sorry.
You okay?
괜찮아? 괜찮아?
괜찮은거야?
You okay? You okay?
I am now.
포커하겠다고 내 친구를 팔아먹었어
Ah, poker night.
And all I had to do
was rat out my best friend.
I saw that, Grimes.
다 봤어요, 그라임즈
걱정마요
Oh, don't worry.
맥주 몇 캔 없이 하는 카드게임이
무슨 재미겠어요?
What's a card game without
a couple of brewskis?
몇 캔이라면..
14캔이요?
And by "couple,"
do you mean 14?
세상에
Oh, God.
Mmm. Mmm!
I won't forget the loyalty
you showed, Grimes.
오늘 해준 일은
절대 잊지 않겠어요
Tonight, we drink.
오늘 밤엔 우리가 마시지만
내일은 바토스키가 마시게 될거예요
Tomorrow,
Bartowski gets his.
Whatever, dude.
그러던가요
- 맥주 드려요?
- 아니요
Beer?
Oh, no.
제껀 직접 가져왔답니다
I brought my own. Whoo!
Mmm.
- 고등학교 때 같네요!
- 신나셨구만
Tastes like high school!
- Donkeys wild.
시작하자. 스트립 포커 할 사람?
Let's go-- who's gonna put
the "poker" in "strip poker."
해봅시다 여러분
해보자고
Let's play it out, boys,
let's play it out.
정말 괜찮으세요?
Are you sure you're okay?
네 그런것 같네요
I think so.
평소에도 다 이런가요?
Is this a normal day
at the office for you?
네. 케이시가 노래한것만 빼면요
Yeah, except Casey
doesn't usually sing.
자 우선 반역죄로 널 체포할거야
Okay, first I'm gonna
have you arrested
for crimes
against your country.
그리고 널 기트모로 끌고가서
(쿠바에 있는 관타나모 미 해군기지)
Then I'll take you down
to Club Gitmo,
애들하고 다같이 널..
hang you up by your fingernails
with the boys...
협박하는건 고마워요
정말 고마운데
Hey! I appreciate the threats,
I really do.
But can I please explain myself?
내가 설명 하게 해줄래요?
뭘 설명해? 적한테
기밀 정보를 넘겼잖아
Explain what? You gave away
classified intel to the enemy.
그 덕에 이젠 누가 풀크럼 요원인지
알 수 없게 됐지
Now we're never gonna know
the identities
of those FULCRUM agents.
내가 설마 정말 줬겠어요
Ye of little faith.
케이시, 날 좀 믿어봐요
Casey, come on, buddy.
내가 복사도 안하고
그냥 그 사람한테 넘겼겠어요?
Do you really think that I would
give that guy
the list to destroy
before I made myself a copy?
Q-36 게임 카피어예요
Hey.
Q-36 game copier.
다행스럽게도 모건이
치사하고 양심이 없어서
Thankfully, Morgan is
too cheap and unethical
돈 내고 게임을 사는 법이 없거든요
to pay for his own
video game entertainment.
Canada's greatest gift
since Shania Twain.
샤니아 트웨인 이후
캐나다에서 받은 최고의 선물이죠
구해주셔서 고마워요
Thank you for
saving my life.
Sorry for not
trusting you with Chuck.
아까 그 얘기
믿지 않았던 것도 죄송하고요
You want to pay me back?
보답하고 싶으세요?
Don't hurt him again.
그럼 척한테 다신 상처 주지 마세요
I won't.
네
I wouldn't.
그럴 일 없을거예요
I care about Chuck.
척을 좋아해요
Me, too.
저도요
It's my job to protect him.
척을 보호하는게 제 일이예요
From anything.
모든것으로부터요
Hey, Emmett.
안녕하세요 에밋
Stop screaming.
소리 지르지 마요
Wow.
Little too much fun
last night, huh, pal?
어젯밤 때문에 힘든가봐요?
어제 퍼지 네이블(칵테일 이름)을
또 마시는게 아니었어요
I should never have gone
for that second Fuzzy Navel.
That wine cooler had
four percent alcohol.
그 칵테일의 4%가 알코올이래요
네 저도 알아요
I know. I know.
있잖아요
I tell you what, though,
let's talk about it,
제 사무실에 가서 얘기 좀 하죠
in my office.
Yeah, come on.
This way.
어서요. 이쪽이예요
우리가 개발한 기술이
하나 있는데 알려줄게요
You know, I wanted to
talk to you today about
a little technique
that we developed around here.
해리 탱이 있을 땐 기가 막히게 먹혔죠
(예전 대머리 부매니저 기억하시죠?)
It worked wonders
during the Harry Tang years.
Can we talk about this
some other time, Grimes?
이 얘기 나중에 해도 되죠?
You see, BuyMoria
바이모리아는 법치 국가예요
is a country
governed by law.
But occasionally, a
vigilante hero has to rise
하지만 때로는
영웅 자경단원이 나타나서
and take that law
into his own hands to protect
사랑하는 조국을 지키기 위해
그 법을 손에 쥐려하죠
the country
that he loves.
This is from last night.
이건 어젯밤 영상이예요
After poker.
포커 게임후요
I'm Big Mike!
내가 빅 마이크다!
What you doing here, Emmett?!
여기서 뭐하나 에밋?!
Is that you in Big Mike's office
after hours?
근무시간 후에 빅 마이크
사무실에 있는 사람, 당신인가요?
That's weird,
because
이상하네요
출입금지 구역인줄 알았거든요
I thought that was off-limits.
Even to you.
당신한테도요
I didn't go six years
내가 꼬맹이들 부매니저나 하려고
전문대를 6년이나 다닌줄 알아!
to community college
to assistant manage
a bunch of register jockeys!
Oh, man, you do not look good.
이런, 상태가 안 좋네요
Now, I know
that we're...
우리 둘이..
countrymen
and all.
같은 곳 출신이죠
그래서 사람들에게 이걸 보이고 싶진 않아요
I hate to have to run
this up the flagpole.
You wouldn't.
- 설마 보여주진 않겠죠
- 아니긴 왜 아니야
Damn right I would.
당장 척한테 하는
마녀 사냥 그만 두지 않으면
If you don't call off
this witch hunt
for Chuck Bartowski,
this goes public.
모두에게 보여줄거야
내 말 알아들어?
Do we understand each other?
Good.
좋아
Viva BuyMoria.
바이모리아 만세
Tastes like high school.
꼭 고등학교 같아요
Okay, computer's back up.
컴퓨터 백업시켰어
It's decoding the list.
Just a matter of time
해독중이야. 이제 풀크럼 요원
명단을 얻는건 시간문제야
before we learn the identities
of FULCRUM's agents.
Ooh.
Oh!
Hey. Hey, yeah, hey.
괜찮아. 어차피
벗으려고 했던건데 뭐
That's fine, I wasn't
gonna pack that one anyway.
Oh, wait. Hey, no.
아 잠시만. 안돼
The hotel's
booked, so...
거기 호텔 예약해뒀으니까
we should probably go
if we're gonna beat traffic!
막히는 시간 피하면
금방 갈 수 있을거야
아님 거긴 좀 나중에 가도 되고
Or we could just get the weekend
started right now.
Uh, what-what about,
what about the...
음 그럼 저기 저건..
Hm... I have some
spy moves of my own.
나도 내 나름의 방법이 있지
또 해보자 이거야?
We're gonna do this again?
You know what?
케이시
척 오늘 힘들었잖아
He had a big day today.
오늘 하루 정도는 그냥 봐주자
How about we give him
a little
break, huh?
Encryption key's been found.
암호를 찾아냈어
Safe at last.
드디어 도망쳤네
자막제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(http://club.nate.com/24)